What are you doing?
I'm making fish out of leaves.
Looking good.
This one's a fish and this one's an octopus.
It's not a starfish?
S-Sorry about that.
Starfish
Bookstore
Rin, want this?
A fish book!
An Illustrated
Guide to Fish
This one's salmon! They're salty!
Are they just food to you?
Look Rin, it's a flounder.
A flounder?
The kind that has both eyes on one side.
Yeah, you're right!
This one looks like a blowfish, doesn't it?
Yeah, it really does.
Daikichi, look.
Hey, don't cheat.
How am I cheating?
It's cheating if you cut them.
I'm not cheating.
I'm just using my grownup skills.
What should I do?
It's all dried up!
The acorn has holes in it!
Holes?
Maybe a bug got to it.
Yeah, that happened to us too.
Reina threw a fit when I told her not to bring acorns in the house.
So what did you do?
To keep the leaves from drying up and bugs from getting out of the acorns.
Us?
We pressed the leaves.
Pressed them?
I'm back!
Rin, wash your hands first!
One moment!
Daikichi, I'm leaving.
Leaf Aquarium